Joaquín Fiorio

Full Stack Developer

I am a Full-Stack Blockchain developer, with different knowledge of UI/UX design software and Web3 development through smart contracts.



Employment History

Front-Edn Developer at Orbe-Studios, Pergamino

SEPTEMBER 2022 - PRESENT

Creation of design, development and maintenance of the code for a web page and web application for the purchase, sale and administration of NFTs. Knowledge of agile methodologies, SCRUM, was used to carry out these tasks.

Website: https://quantum12.netlify.app/

Web application: https://quantumdapp.netlify.app/

Project manager and Full-Stack Developer at HFTX, Pergamino

JUNE 2022 – JANUARY 2023

Creation, development and maintenance of a web page and financial web application to manage investments in the blockchain through smart contracts, Back-End in MONGODB and NODE.JS and a Front-End based on Angular. Process manager and personnel recruiter for the project.

Website: https://hftxvault.netlify.app/

Web application: https://hftx-test.netlify.app/

Education

Full Stack at Linkedin, Pergamino

JULY 2021 – OCTOBER 2022

I finished the Full-Stack career as Self-taught through different resources that provided me with the necessary skills to be able to develop large-scale projects.

Lawyer at UNR - Law School, Rosario

FEBRUARY 2019 - PRESENT

3rd year advanced law student in the city of Rosario.

Courses

Details

Pergamino, Argentina +5492477358701 joaquin.fiorio@hotmail.com

Links

Financial Application
Financial Application website
NFTs managment Application
NFTs managment website
Marketing Website
Blog
Artisan products website

Skills

Git

MongoDB

Node.js

JavaScript

Bootstrap

jQuery

CSS3

Angular

CSS

HTML5

Full Stack at Linkedin

AUGUST 2021 - OCTOBER 2022

Business Inteligence at UTN - Buenos Aires

JANUARY 2021 – APRIL 2021

Web Development at Platzi

JUNE 2022 – AUGUST 2022

Web multiple lenguages at Udemy

NOVEMBER 2022 - DECEMBER 2022

Progressive Web Applications at Linkedin

SEPTEMBER 2022 - NOVEMBER 2023

Dev-Ops at Linkedin

JANUARY 2023 - FEBRUARY 2023

Fundamentals of programming: API and web services at Linkedin

DECEMBER 2023 - JANUARY 2023

Angular Developer at Linkedin

NOVEMBER 2022 – JANUARY 2023

NODE.JS Developer at Linkedin

OCTOBER 2022 - DECEMBER 2022

About Me

I am a proactive, creative and orderly person. Ability to work in a team, ability to adapt and learn.

Currently I have almost 2 years of experience as a Front-End developer and 3 months as a Full-Stack developer. I am looking for a job in a dependency relationship to demonstrate my desire, motivation and knowledge for this profession.

Contact

Linkedin: https://www.linkedin.com/in/joaquin-fiorio/

Email: joaquin.fiorio@hotmail.com

Solidity

API REST

Hobbies

In my free time I find myself starting a project called CryptoMc and HFTX. Both provided me with many experiences, such as communicating with clients and potential investors in the best way, practicing English when transmitting and developing an idea, programming and design skills, elaboration of strategies and Marketing campaigns, decision making and solution proposals, analytical skills, planning and organization, among others.

links:

https://cryptomcgame.netlify.app/ https://cryptomc.site/

Languages

English

Spanish

References

Gustavo RodriguezfromHFTX +1(325)6328117

GregoriofromOrbe-Studios +50760960926

